http://www.segalco.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Introduction The Segal Group operates the segalco.com website, which provides the SERVICE.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service, the The Segal Group Web site.
At The Segal Group we respect your right to privacy.
We may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of this Web site, download free information or request information.We will guard the personal information you share with us to ensure the content and services that we provide on this Web site are always tailored to your current, designated preferences.
Log Data We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our website uses these "cookies" to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Children Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Marketing & Email When you provide The Segal Group with your name, email address, mailing address, or telephone number, The Segal Group and The Segal Group's representatives may use the provided information to alert you to special offers, updated information, new services, and other information, unless you indicate that you would not like to receive these notices. Beyond its representatives, The Segal Group does not offer or allow the selling of any user-provided information to third parties.
The Segal Group respects the rights users give us when opting to receive email communications and enforces internal policies to preserve those rights. It is our objective to retain the long-term ability to continue to communicate with our users. If you do not want The Segal Group or The Segal Group's representatives to contact you, you may "opt out" of this preference at any time, whether online or by contacting The Segal Group directly. As part of your preference flexibility, you'll always have the option to opt back in and have The Segal Group contact you based on your previous or new preferences.
If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still visit most areas of The Segal Group Web site; however, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification.
External Sites The Segal Group Web site may contain links to other sites. The Segal Group assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of such Web sites. The Segal Group encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy practices may differ from ours.
Contact Us If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us
Don't miss out. Join 16,000 others who already get the latest insights from Segal.
Submit an RFP
Office Locations
Contact Us
Consulting Services
Retirement & Financial Security
Health & Welfare Benefits
Benefits Administration
Benefit Audits
Careers
© 2020 by The Segal Group, Inc.Terms & Conditions Privacy Policy Sitemap Disclosure of Compensation
We use cookies to collect information about how you use segalco.com. We use this information to make the website work as well as possible and improve our offering to you.
Close
